http://www.hpfb.org/privacy

MENU
HomeDonate NowAbout About HPFBBoard of DirectorsEmploymentFrom the Food Bank (blog)Map the Meal GapPress RoomWho We AreFood & Fund DrivePrograms EthicsPointKids CafeNutrition EducationSenior Adult Food ProgramSNAP AssistanceTexas Panhandle VOADThe GardenAgencies Become an AgencyAgency ResourcesVolunteer Product Recovery VolunteersThe Garden VolunteersMobile Harvest VolunteersGet HelpEvents Current Events and PromotionsGolf TournamentTogether We Can!
Privacy Policy
High Plains Food Bank Privacy PolicyThank you for visiting the High Plains Food Bank website. The protection of your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for our website www.hpfb.org. Our Commitment to Your Privacy and SecurityHigh Plains Food Bank is committed to protecting the privacy and the security of your personal information. This privacy policy describes the kind of information we collect from you, how that information is used, and what kind of security measures we employ on our website. We will not sell, share, or rent the information you provide to us in any way that has not been specified in our privacy policy. If you have questions regarding this privacy policy or the High Plains Food Bank’s information practices, please e-mail us at webmaster@hpfb.org. Information Collection and UseHigh Plains Food Bank requests information from you at various points on our website. You are under no obligation to enter any information on our website to participate in some of the opportunities and services we offer at or through High Plains Food Bank. However, registration for volunteer shifts, food & fund drives, events, making online donations, signing up for email newsletters, etc. requires such information collection. Below is a summary of the information we typically collect from you and how it is used. Because we constantly strive to bring new and better services to the community, the list below may not reflect all the most current service offerings for which information is collected. We’ll do our best to update this policy as we provide new services, so please check back often.Volunteers: When you become a volunteer for the High Plains Food Bank, we ask you to provide us your name, telephone number, mailing address, e-mail address, date of birth, and employer or organizational affiliation, if applicable. We use this information to populate our volunteer database and to contact you in regard to High Plains Food Bank volunteer opportunities and activities.Donations: When you give a financial donation to the High Plains Food Bank, we ask that you provide us with your name, telephone number, mailing address, e-mail address and credit card information. We use a secure third party to process your donation.eNews: When you subscribe to receive our eNews, we ask you for your name, e-mail address and birth month and day. We will share with you HPFB news, events, and opportunities.Surveys and Sign-Up Forms: We occasionally invite people to participate in a survey or to sign-up for certain activities and events.Information SharingHigh Plains Food Bank does not sell, share, or rent donor names and contact information to any third parties. This pertains to any donor information collected both online and offline. Although unlikely, the High Plains Food Bank may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personal information about our users. We will provide this information, to the extent technically possible, upon request and receipt of the appropriate documentation. Disclosure may also occur if we consider it necessary to protect our legal rights, or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct.Access and the Ability to Correct Your InformationThe High Plains Food Bank stores the information you provide upon registration at our site and for our various services in databases. If your information changes, if you no longer desire to volunteer, or you no longer wish to receive information and marketing from High Plains Food Bank, please contact webmaster@hpfb.org to change your information, or mail a written request to 815 Ross, Amarillo, TX 79102. Unsubscribing from our Mailing ListIn order to keep all our supporters informed about the High Plains Food Bank, we send updates on our activities and events, including our eNews. If you are receiving electronic communications from the High Plains Food Bank and you decide at any time that you no longer wish to hear from us, you can use the “unsubscribe” link provided in each email to remove yourself from our mailing list. Or, send a request to be removed via email to webmaster@hpfb.org or mail to 815 Ross, Amarillo, TX 79102.Cookies and Computer InformationOur site and integrated tools use cookies, pixels, and similar technologies to analyze website traffic and performance and to improve the site user experience. We collect non-personally identifiable information (“Aggregate Data”).We collect the following information about your computer configuration: browser type, operating system, IP address, and the URL of the web page you were on just prior to visiting the High Plains Food Bank website. We use this information to analyze usage trends, administer the site, and track our visitors’ movements across our site for aggregate use. This Aggregate Data will not reveal, nor is it associated with, your personal identity.Specifically, collected data is cookie data that is used to assist in creating audiences and attributing actions to specific ad campaigns. Data is stored in vetted third-party platforms that facilitate the collection of this data through secured tags. These platforms all conform to necessary data privacy laws and allow for the exercising of all rights of data subjects. Lastly, platforms that allow for user-level tracking do so only through data gathered with proper consent and obscure any form of user identification.The Site also uses Google Analytics, which provides information about site users’ interests, habits, and other demographic information. Google Analytics does not collect any personally identifiable information about you, and the generic information the system does collect is used only by the High Plains Food Bank for the purpose of better understanding our site visitors and improving your Site experience. You may opt-out of having this information collected through any of several software programs, including Google’s own program at this address: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/Privacy of Children OnlineThe High Plains Food Bank does not intend to collect, maintain, store, or use personal information about children under the age of 13. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Notification of ChangesIf we make a change to our privacy policy, we will post a notice of those changes on the privacy policy section of our web site so that you will always have notice of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner incompatible with the stated purposes at the time it was collected, we will post a prominent notification of the change in policy on our web site.SecurityFor online donation processing, The High Plains Food Bank uses secure data networks protected by industry-standard firewalls and password protection systems. Only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our donors. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as a donor’s credit card number collected for a commerce transaction, is also encrypted prior to transmission. Although the High Plains Food Bank operates secure data networks, no Internet transmission can be guaranteed 100% secure. While we do everything we can to protect your data, you use this site and its services at your own risk.
site navigationHomeDonate NowAboutAbout HPFBBoard of DirectorsEmploymentFrom the Food Bank (blog)Map the Meal GapPress RoomWho We AreFood & Fund DriveProgramsEthicsPointKids CafeNutrition EducationSenior Adult Food ProgramSNAP AssistanceTexas Panhandle VOADThe GardenThe Garden Resources Workshops in the GardenAgenciesBecome an AgencyAgency ResourcesVolunteerProduct Recovery VolunteersThe Garden VolunteersMobile Harvest VolunteersGet HelpEventsCurrent Events and PromotionsGolf TournamentTogether We Can!contact usLocation815 Ross StreetAmarillo, TX 79102Mailing AddressPO BOX 31803Amarillo TX, 79120Main Line(806) 374-8562Fax Line(806) 371-7459Email AddressEmail Follow us!Facebook.com/highplainsfoodbankTwitter: @hpfoodbank Instagram: hpfoodbank
Call Us Today at 806.374.8562
©2020 High Plains Food Bank is a 501(c)(3) private nonprofit organization  |  All Rights Reserved  |  EIN – 75-1838348  |  Privacy Policy
This institution is an equal opportunity provider.  |  Esta institución es un proveedor que ofrece igualdad de oportunidades.
Site powered by
